Le-Anh Tran (1996)

PhD in Computer Vision

"Once the WHY is clear, the HOW goes easy"

😵 tranleanh.github.io 🔽 tranleanh.nt@gmail.com

+82 10 7248 2807 **(7)** github.com/tranleanh

Seoul, South Korea in /in/tranleanh

ABOUT ME -

I began my academic journey in 2014 by pursuing a degree in Automation and Control Engineering, but the appeal of Al captivated me in late 2017. Since then, I have been actively involved in various Al projects. My primary research interests that are reflected by my publications so far include **image enhancement**, **cluster analysis**, and **object detection**. I completed my PhD in early 2024 under the guidance of Prof. Dong-Chul Park, an expert in Artificial Neural Networks. I primarily specialize in **Python** programming and have experience with various frameworks such as **tensorflow**, **pytorch**, **conda**, etc. I also contribute as a writer to various popular online blog platforms such as **Towards Data Science**, Towards Al, etc.

EDUCATION -

3/2021 - 2/2024 PhD in Computer Vision

Myongji University (Natural Science Campus), South Korea

Myongji University (Natural Science Campus), South Korea

9/2014 - 8/2018 BEng in Automation and Control Engineering (graduated with honors)

HCMC University of Technology and Education (HCMUTE), Vietnam

EXPERIENCE

4/2020 - 2/2024 Research Intern

MindinTech, Inc., Seoul, South Korea Area: Computer Vision for Intelligent Driving

3/2021 - 2/2024 Research Assistant

Intelligent Computing Research Lab (ICRL), Myongji University, South Korea

Area: Image Enhancement, Cluster Analysis

7/2019 - 9/2019 **Summer Internship**

OCST Co., Ltd., Seoul, South Korea

Project: Object Detection Streaming and Data Management on Web Browser

3/2018 - 2/2019 Al Engineer

FPT Software, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam Area: Computer Vision for Autonomous Driving

2/2017 - 1/2018 **Teaching Assistant**

Faculty of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, HCMUTE, Vietnam

Subject: Electric Drivers

OTHERS

Languages

- Vietnamese (native)
- English (proficient)

Memberships

- IEEE Member (since 2022)
- IEEE Young Professionals (since 2022)

Work Style

- Being self-motivated and independent
- Moving from basic to complex
- Being able to learn new knowledge quickly
- Being a problem solver

PUBLICATIONS	
2024	Cluster Analysis via Projection onto Convex Sets LA Tran, D Kwon, HM Deberneh, DC Park Intelligent Data Analysis, IOS Press (SCIE)
2024	Toward Improving Robustness of Object Detectors Against Domain Shift LA Tran, NC Tran, DC Park, J Carrabina, D Castells-Rufas IEEE International Conference on Green Energy, Computing and Sustainable Technology (GECOST)
2023	Single Image Dehazing via Regional Saturation-Value Translation LA Tran, D Kwon, DC Park Procedia Computer Science
2023	Image Compression using POCS-based Clustering Algorithm LA Tran, DC Park International Exchange and Innovation Conference on Engineering & Sciences (IEICES)
2023	Embedding Clustering via Autoencoder and Projection onto Convex Set LA Tran, TD Nguyen, TD Do, NC Tran, D Kwon, DC Park IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2023	Efficient Infrared-Thermal Imaging Fusion for Human Detection in Heavy Smoke Scenarios NN Truong, MH Le, TD Do, LA Tran, TD Nguyen, HH Trinh IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2023	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map: Robustness and Applicability LA Tran, DC Park Smart Innovation, Systems and Technologies, Vol. 333
2022	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map: Architecture LA Tran, DC Park International Conference on Advances in Signal Processing and Artificial Intelligence (ASPAI)
2022	POCS-based Clustering Algorithm LA Tran, HM Deberneh, TD Do, TD Nguyen, MH Le, DC Park IEEE International Workshop on Intelligent Systems (IWIS)
2022	Encoder-Decoder Network with Guided Transmission Map for Image Dehazing LA Tran, S Moon, DC Park Procedia Computer Science, Vol. 204
2021	Enhancement of Robustness in Object Detection Module for ADAS LA Tran, TD Do, DC Park, MH Le IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2020	Object Detection Streaming and Data Management on Web Browser LA Tran Technical Report, OCST Co., Ltd.
2019	Robust U-Net-based Road Lane Markings Detection for Autonomous Driving LA Tran, MH Le IEEE International Conference on System Science and Engineering (ICSSE)
2018	A Vision-based Method for Autonomous Landing on a Target with a Quadcopter LA Tran, NP Le, TD Do, MH Le IEEE International Conference on Green Technology and Sustainable Development (GTSD)
Under Review	Distilled Pooling Transformer Encoder for Efficient Image Dehazing LA Tran, DC Park
Under Review	Encoder-Decoder Networks with Guided Transmission Map for Effective Image Dehazing LA Tran, DC Park
Under Review	Haze Removal via Regional Saturation-Value Translation and Soft Segmentation LA Tran, DC Park
Under Review	Soft Knowledge-based Distilled Dehazing Networks LA Tran, DC Park